(yea let's go) (pull up) (smoking that kush) End yo' block, I roll 'em, roll 'em (whoo)
Shoot that shot, I'm scorin', scorin' (whoo)
This Biscotti got me floatin' Can't take what you give, you gotta give 'em what I deserveCan't fuck
with nobody (what?) Not even my shadow (yeah, no one)
I got on Ed Hardy (what? What? What? What? What?) was just smokin' that Kush, countin' money, can't
fit in rubber bands Took the bands to the store, see it, I cop it Hop in that
whip and I'm dust 'em like, skrr (ah)
Brand new ice, on air, bitch, I could never think twice, oh, yeah (yeah)
Tell 'em, "Put the price up, yeah"
Tall ass money, get your height up (yeah-yeah, woah)
Countin' his crypto, yeah, woah
That shit got me jammed up, yeah (woah)
Booted up, end up, yeah (huh)
Fuck around and light your camp up, yeah Whole lotta bands in the duffle like- (yeah) (run it
back...) (yea let's go) (pull up) (smoking that kush) End yo' block, I roll 'em, roll 'em (whoo)
Shoot that shot, I'm scorin', scorin' (whoo)
This Biscotti got me floatin' Can't take what you give, you gotta give 'em what I deserveCan't fuck
with nobody (what?) Not even my shadow (yeah, no one)
I got on Ed Hardy (what? What? What? What? What?) was just smokin' that Kush, countin' money, can't
fit in rubber bands Took the bands to the store, see it, I cop it Hop in that
whip and I'm dust 'em like, skrr (ah)
Brand new ice, on air, bitch, I could never think twice, oh, yeah (yeah)
Tell 'em, "Put the price up, yeah"
Tall ass money, get your height up (yeah-yeah, woah)
Countin' his crypto, yeah, woah
That shit got me jammed up, yeah (woah)
Booted up, end up, yeah (huh)
Fuck around and light your camp up, yeah Whole lotta bands in the duffle like- (yeah)
So much fuckin' money just countin', I'ma need more hands
I'ma need a new backpack and some bigger pants They told me I'm fishin' like Scotty
In the next year, yeah, I'll be the highest (highest) Yeah, I put that ho in Prada, and
after, I made her holler
And my bro took off your mans, I heard that was your top shotter
I got Vetements on my pants and my shirt Balenciaga
Huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh You don't want no smoke, bitch, FN Five-seveN shoot
a opp in his dome
Hit that boy in his chest, hit his heart, now it's chrome (hearts) I'ma keep it player (brah)
Come through popping shit off, hell yeah (hell yeah, yea). don't believe in the hype (nah, nah)
Remember that money was tight (yeah)
And then that boy money got right (yeah) Yeah, I'm on shit (yeah, shit)
I was taking trips to LA, tryna hit (hit)
That money getting spent (okay, okay, fah)
I'm on shit (graah, go) (LET'S GOO)
So much fuckin' money just countin', I'ma need more hands
I'ma need a new backpack and some bigger pants They told me I'm fishin' like Scotty
In the next year, yeah, I'll be the highest (highest) Yeah, I put that ho in Prada, and
after, I made her holler
And my bro took off your mans, I heard that was your top shotter
I got Vetements on my pants and my shirt Balenciaga
Huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh, huh You don't want no smoke, bitch, FN Five-seveN shoot
a opp in his dome
Hit that boy in his chest, hit his heart, now it's chrome (hearts) I'ma keep it player (brah)
Come through popping shit off, hell yeah (hell yeah, yea). don't believe in the hype (nah, nah)
Remember that money was tight (yeah)
And then that boy money got right (yeah) Yeah, I'm on shit (yeah, shit)
I was taking trips to LA, tryna hit (hit)
That money getting spent (okay, okay, fah)
I'm on shit (graah, go)